https://www.bradninchcc.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Fixtures
Bradninch Cricket Club (“Bradninch Cricket Club“) operates bradninchcc.org.uk and may operate other websites. It is Bradninch Cricket Club’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, Bradninch Cricket Club collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Bradninch Cricket Club’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Bradninch Cricket Club’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Bradninch Cricket Club may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
Bradninch Cricket Club also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on bradninchcc.org.uk blogs/sites. Bradninch Cricket Club only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to Bradninch Cricket Club’s websites choose to interact with Bradninch Cricket Club in ways that require Bradninch Cricket Club to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Bradninch Cricket Club gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at bradninchcc.org.uk to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Bradninch Cricket Club are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Bradninch Cricket Club collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Bradninch Cricket Club. Bradninch Cricket Club does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
Bradninch Cricket Club may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Bradninch Cricket Club may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Bradninch Cricket Club does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
Bradninch Cricket Club discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Bradninch Cricket Club’s behalf or to provide services available at Bradninch Cricket Club’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Bradninch Cricket Club’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Bradninch Cricket Club will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Bradninch Cricket Club discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Bradninch Cricket Club believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Bradninch Cricket Club, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Bradninch Cricket Club website and have supplied your email address, Bradninch Cricket Club may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Bradninch Cricket Club and our products. If you send us a request (for example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Bradninch Cricket Club takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Bradninch Cricket Club uses cookies to help Bradninch Cricket Club identify and track visitors, their usage of Bradninch Cricket Club website, and their website access preferences. Bradninch Cricket Club visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Bradninch Cricket Club’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Bradninch Cricket Club’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Bradninch Cricket Club may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Bradninch Cricket Club’s sole discretion. Bradninch Cricket Club encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a bradninchcc.org.uk account, you might also receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Report issues with this page
Issue:								*
Incorrect spelling
Page display/formatting
Copyright Infringement
Spam
Invalid Contents
Broken Links
There are no upcoming events.
